Help on module Function Drawer:

NAME
    Function Drawer

FUNCTIONS
    function_drawer()
        Display a graphic interface containing:
        - place to enter a function formulas
        - keyboard with symbols, arithmetic operators and elementary functions
        - plot image
        - possibility to change the settings of the plot
        Convert the entered formulas to functions and draw their plots in the given x-range.
        If the formula or x limits are incorrect, display an error message.

FILE
    c:\users\szymo\folder\function drawer\function drawer.py


